‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎NORTH HAMGYONG PROVINCE, NORTH KOREA
‎EPISODE 4
‎GEUMGANG ORPHANAGE
‎Nice to meet you.
‎I'm Major Ri Eung Ryeong
‎of the Democratic People's Republic
‎of Korea.
‎I hear that you're the most agile
‎and physically fit students here.
‎If you think you're the best of them all
‎and want to become a member
‎of the Republic's athletic corps,
‎step forward.
‎If I become a member,
‎will I be able to eat my fill?
‎You will.
‎YOUNG REVOLUTIONARIES
‎OF THE LEARNING-FIRST DOCTRINE
‎Move the desks.
‎You're the only one who passed.
‎Tell me your name.
‎Park Yeong Gwang, sir.
‎Take him to the car.
‎Yes, sir.
‎That one passes too.
‎A warrior of the Republic
‎ought to have that kind of tenacity.
‎Hey.
‎What's your name?
‎Kim…
‎ARMED WITH REVOLUTIONARY SPIRIT
‎Stand straight! Attention!
‎All of you have become official members
‎of the Special Operations Unit
‎of the Democratic People's Republic
‎of Korea.
‎Our goal
‎is to infiltrate the South
‎and bring back the heads
‎of their leading officials!
‎Take them to the torture chamber.
‎-We are the people's army
‎-and warriors of belief and conviction.
‎Stop!
‎You still think
‎this is the athletic corps?
‎This is hell.
‎You'll either survive
‎and become an operative,
‎or you'll die and become pig feed!
‎It's one or the other.
‎Number 66.
‎What's your name?
‎I don't remember, sir.
‎Number 73.
‎What's your name?
‎Kim…
‎I only know that my last name is Kim.
‎This bastard still doesn't get it.
‎Wild animals don't have names!
‎None of you have first or last names.
‎Do you understand?
‎Do you?!
‎-Defend with our lives!
‎-Hurry up! Get over here!
‎Right now!
‎Hurry up!
‎Get it together!
‎-Hurry up!
‎-Speed it up.
‎Hurry up!
‎Fire!
‎CRUSH THE PROVOCATIVE SCHEMES
‎OF THE SOUTH KOREAN PUPPETS!
‎Enough.
‎Number 66.
‎You are truly
‎the Republic's finest warrior.
‎Well done.
‎Forget it.
‎Take it away.
‎I'm not giving it to you out of pity.
‎You keep losing to me,
‎so I was wondering
‎if it's because you don't eat enough.
‎Get lost.
‎Come on. We're from the same orphanage.
‎Don't let pride get in the way
‎between comrades.
‎You bastard!
‎Go stuff your own face!
‎Those two are at it again! Stop them!
‎-Stop it!
‎-Stop!
‎-Hey, stop!
‎-Let go of him!
‎-Stop already!
‎-That bastard!
‎COMBAT READINESS IS A REVOLUTIONARY DUTY
‎Next.
‎…NUMBER 85, NUMBER 18, NUMBER 44
‎This operation is a joint operation,
‎so it comes with a bigger reward.
‎You will complete it successfully
‎and return to our country as heroes.
‎-Democratic People's Republic of Korea!
‎GANGWON PROVINCE, REPUBLIC OF KOREA
‎Wait.
‎Your brother was the best operative
‎this unit has ever seen.
‎But during a mission,
‎some rat-bastard stabbed him in the back
‎and got him killed.
‎That rat-bastard traitor
‎killed all of his comrades,
‎stole the number 66 from your brother,
‎and became a lapdog for the South!
‎Yeong Gwang!
‎Don't leave me behind!
‎-Yeong Gwang!
‎-Wait for me!
‎I promise to succeed
‎and come back for you!
‎Stay alive!
‎You have to survive, okay?
‎-Wait for me, Gang Seong!
‎-Yeong Gwang!
‎Yeong Gwang!
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎Here you are.
‎Fake 66.
‎Damn it.
‎Don't move!
‎Hands up.
‎Hands up!
‎Put the gun down.
‎Times sure have changed.
‎-Wait, slow down.
‎-Why?
‎There's the clue.
‎Slow, slow.
‎I said put it down.
‎Hands on your head.
‎Get down on your knees.
‎Who are these sharp people
‎I'd like to thank?
‎The woman is my co-worker,
‎and the man…
‎is the owner of my local dry cleaner.
‎What?
‎You don't seem surprised,
‎so I guess you already knew.
‎I expected someone would be watching me.
‎I suggest you surrender…
‎Number 66.
‎Mr. Kim.
‎You violated your contract
‎with the government.
‎Please surrender.
‎Min-ji…
‎has been kidnapped.
‎Please wait until I find her.
‎Once I do, I'll turn myself in.
‎I give you my word.
‎No, wait…
‎Mr. Kim!
‎Are you okay? How bad is it?
‎Bulletproof vest…
‎I thought you were dead!
‎Hey, help me up.
‎Hurry up and come out.
‎I just got shot!
‎Don't be such a crybaby!
‎That was a close call.
‎You sure know how to stay busy.
‎When did you get shot?
‎Han-soo, do you have a trauma kit?
‎It should be under the back…
‎Let's go to a hospital.
‎It's fine, it's just a graze.
‎Keep going.
‎Just go.
‎You just got hit in the side by a bullet.
‎Getting grazed still counts
‎as getting shot, doesn't it?
‎Are you sure you'll be okay?
‎Right here! Let me off here.
‎Yes, right here.
‎This is good. Thank you!
‎Hey!
‎Has the bleeding even stopped?
‎Stop!
‎No!
‎What's going on?
‎That punk…
‎Why you little…
‎You almost killed me!
‎What are you, a damn deer?
‎-You bumped me! I felt it!
‎-Why pop out of nowhere like that?!
‎Let me talk first! Hey!
‎What's going on?
‎What happened to Min-ji? Where is she?
‎Who are these bastards?
‎Who are they?!
‎Who the hell…
‎Who are these damn bastards?!
‎They're dead meat!
‎Damn it!
‎-Hey, is it okay if I break this?
‎-Careful with that!
‎Goddamn it!
‎I'm good. Let's focus now.
‎Hey, are you okay?
‎Are you…
‎Hey!
‎You already got attacked?!
‎That's a gunshot wound, right?
‎I told you to be careful!
‎What were you two going to do without me?
‎I'm here now, so don't worry.
‎Don't worry.
‎Just think of it
‎as an extra hole in your body
‎and tough it out.
‎So nostrils, ears, and bullet wounds
‎are all just holes, huh?
‎They're all the same to you, aren't they?
‎I'm just saying.
‎Come on, we've been shot at before!
‎Just keep driving.
‎Are you okay?
‎By the way, where are we going?
‎Hwasin Station to find a homeless guy.
‎The homeless guy who found Min-ji's phone.
‎SEONMIN-EUP
‎Codename 66's current location.
‎8-3, Gongdan-gil, Seonmin-eup.
‎Park Jin-cheol has joined them.
‎-Step on it.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Hey.
‎Let's hurry.
‎Hey, you.
‎Go buy me a bottle of soju.
‎Damn it. Why aren't you going?
‎Want me to teach you a lesson, you punk?
‎-Dad!
‎-Come here!
‎-You little punk.
‎-What's wrong?
‎-This man was shouting at me.
‎-Yeah?
‎What is it? What about him?
‎He went off on me.
‎Hey, mister. You sleeping?
‎Hey, mister!
‎Who are you?
‎You remember this phone, right?
‎I heard you traded it
‎for a bottle of soju.
‎Did I?
‎Why do you ask?
‎-Where did you get it?
‎-He probably stole it.
‎"Stole it"?
‎Look.
‎I'm not a thief!
‎I found it!
‎When and where did you find it?
‎Why do I have to tell you that?
‎Because it's still illegal
‎to sell something you found.
‎Should I call the cops?
‎Yeah, go ahead.
‎Three men are threatening
‎an innocent citizen.
‎I'll call them myself.
‎Let's just beat him until he talks.
‎That's not a bad idea,
‎but too many people will see us.
‎There's an alley over there.
‎Just wait here.
‎I'll escort him and be right back.
‎-Why don't you come with me?
‎-No, wait.
‎-Come on.
‎-He threw it away.
‎Some guy threw it away,
‎and I picked it up.
‎Did you see his face?
‎This looks expensive.
‎Hey, mister.
‎Ta-da.
‎Want to trade?
‎What exactly did I do wrong?
‎The owner threw it away in the trash can.
‎Sir.
‎Do you remember anything about the car?
‎The plate number, model, or color?
‎What about his appearance or build?
‎How many people was he with?
‎How am I supposed to remember all that?
‎Please try to remember. Please.
‎I'm begging you.
‎The car was…
‎It was a white BMV.
‎I didn't see the plate number.
‎What time was it?
‎It was at night.
‎I don't know the exact time.
‎Oh.
‎He had a man bun.
‎That's all I know.
‎Jeez.
‎The weather at Myeongpo Port
‎will be mostly clear during the day,
‎but it will turn cloudy starting tonight.
‎Caution is advised as localized downpours,
‎along with thunder and lightning,
‎are expected tonight.
‎Hello, boss.
‎Hey.
‎Good job securing the warehouse.
‎-Thank you, sir.
‎-Is it this way?
‎Have you eaten yet?
‎Yes, I did.
‎Hey, Gang-min. Have we eaten yet?
‎No, we haven't had a single meal today.
‎Man, the kid here says he already ate.
‎It's like he doesn't give a damn
‎if I starve to death or not.
‎I'm sorry, sir.
‎I'm just kidding.
‎What did you have?
‎I had blood sausage soup, sir.
‎Was it good?
‎It wasn't bad, sir.
‎Then you should wash it down
‎with some water!
‎Hurry the hell up if you're done drinking!
‎-Everyone else will be here soon!
‎-Sir!
‎Should we move the body, boss?
‎Let's eat first, you punk.
‎Sounds good, sir.
‎We don't know the exact time,
‎so look for the homeless man.
‎Okay.
‎A white BMV…
‎There. Found him.
‎You did? Who is it? Do you see his face?
‎Just a second.
‎It's loading.
‎Kim Sang-man, 41 years old.
‎-Eight priors?
‎-What?
‎Eight priors?
‎Eight priors for violent crimes?
‎Are you serious?
‎Hold on.
‎He got out of the back seat.
‎-That means there were others.
‎-Okay.
‎If we plug in the vehicle search data
‎to track its location…
‎Just a second.
‎It's searching in real-time,
‎so it'll take a moment to load.
‎How dare they do that to Min-ji?
‎Kim Sang-man.
‎Speed bump.
‎You idiot!
‎You're killing me.
‎We brought the body
‎and secured a location.
‎Now all that's left
‎is to drop this bombshell on Ju Gang-chan.
‎"Hey, Gang-chan."
‎"Your daughter…
‎killed a person."
‎But sir,
‎why are you so obsessed with Ju Gang-chan?
‎Did he screw you over big time
‎a while back or something?
‎Boss, here's a big potato for you.
‎You little!
‎I'm sorry, sir!
‎Please forgive me!
‎9 YEARS AGO
‎-No to redevelopment!
‎-Go away!
‎-Bring it on.
‎All of you!
‎STOP RECONSTRUCTION
‎THAT DESTROYS CITIZENS' LIVES
‎Do you know how old these apartments are?
‎I'm not sure, sir.
‎Forty years.
‎These 40-year-old apartments
‎still aren't approved for reconstruction.
‎You and I both need that approval
‎to make a fortune.
‎Don't you agree?
‎Boss.
‎How many apartments these days
‎still don't have underground parking?
‎We're at the scene at Midu Apartments
‎where a cleaning service employee fell.
‎Employee A
‎fell off the railing and was transported
‎to the hospital for surgery,
‎but hasn't regained consciousness.
‎Concerns are mounting over building safety
‎as residents describe the hallways
‎as unsafe due to low railings.
‎With cracks appearing
‎across the exterior walls,
‎many say that simple repairs
‎can no longer hold the building together.
‎Midu Apartments' reconstruction
‎has been approved after years of setbacks.
‎The Seoul Metropolitan Government
‎announced on the 19th
‎that they have passed the decision
‎to authorize the reconstruction plan
‎for the 40-year-old Midu Apartments.
‎According to experts, this authorization…
‎I didn't have a choice.
‎I was ordered to do it.
‎Jung-dae,
‎please forgive me just this once.
‎Jung-dae, please!
‎I didn't want to take over like this.
‎CEO YANG SEOK-CHEOL
‎Who knew it was so damn easy
‎to become the boss?
‎I should've done this sooner.
‎Just trust me
‎and don't waver.
‎Here's a toast
‎to our future.
‎-Cheers!
‎-Bring in the band.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Boss, you got a call.
‎Everyone, be quiet.
‎Who's this?
‎This is the executive office
‎of Juhak Construction.
‎The chairman would like to see you.
‎I heard there was a new head
‎of the company.
‎I didn't know
‎it was the guy under Mr. Yang.
‎I guess you're pretty capable
‎for a young guy.
‎I look forward to working with you.
‎There's a lot I need you to do for me.
‎I forgot all about you for a minute there.
‎It was you, right?
‎The bastard
‎who ordered Mr. Yang to kill me.
‎It's okay.
‎I think there's a misunderstanding.
‎I never ordered him to do that.
‎I just muttered to myself
‎that I wished someone would die there.
‎What?
‎I have to say…
‎Mr. Yang was quite an incompetent man.
‎Look at you. You're still alive.
‎Crush him.
‎Bring it!
‎Die, you asshole!
‎When I was young,
‎my next-door neighbor had a huge dog.
‎But you see, the dog was vicious
‎and bit their owner a few times.
‎The owner couldn't take it anymore
‎and was about to put it down.
‎But I convinced them that I could tame it.
‎You see, I liked the dog
‎because it was vicious.
‎Do you know how I tamed it?
‎I made sure it could never bite its owner.
‎Open your mouth.
‎Do you feel like wagging your tail now?
‎I could also pour boiling water
‎down your throat
‎and make sure you can't even bark.
‎I'll do anything.
‎I'll do whatever you want.
‎I'll become your dog, sir.
‎Please don't kill me.
‎Please spare me.
‎The sun's down.
‎Let's wrap up here and move the body.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Jeez, what kind of thug walks on eggshells
‎after taking a few hits?
‎Did it hurt a lot?
‎No, sir. I'm okay, sir!
‎We're here, boss.
‎I know that, idiot!
‎Yes, sir!
‎This dead body weighs a ton, boss.
‎Stop whining.
‎Excuse me.
‎What are you doing?
‎What's that?
‎-It's a dead body.
‎-What?
‎A dead body?
‎You should've gone to bed early, old man.
‎Hey, Sang-man.
‎Yes, boss.
‎It's not what you think, sir.
‎We rented this cold storage warehouse.
‎Let me show you the contract.
‎Where was it again?
‎Hey!
‎Still nothing?
‎How much longer will it take?
‎Almost there. 80%.
‎Now at 81%.
‎Jeez, it's taking forever.
‎Oh boy, this is heavy.
‎Now at 95%.
‎Okay, 96%.
‎What's that?
‎Isn't that Mole Cricket?
‎What?
‎MYEONGPO PORT, REPUBLIC OF KOREA
‎Hey, Kim.
‎I know you're not dead, so come out.
‎Stalling will only make things
‎worse for you.
‎You know you're better off coming with me
‎than being dragged to the North to die.
‎Come on out!
‎Not you. I want Kim.
‎Hurry up!
‎You know,
‎I didn't like you the moment you showed up
‎wearing that fedora.
‎You have no idea
‎how big of a mistake you just made.
‎I'm extremely angry right now,
‎and I'm going to express that anger.
‎Give me a second.
‎-What are you doing?
‎-You know,
‎my knees
‎and my back hurt, so I can't do it much.
‎But I feel like I should do it today,
‎and I think I can.
‎Stop playing games and get out of the way.
‎Don't you know who I am, you bastard?
‎You?
‎Mole…
‎Mole Rat, right?
‎You're a mole rat.
‎I bet you got that fedora off the streets.
‎It worked.
‎I did it.
‎You see that?
‎You think a fancy move like that
‎would work in a real fight?
‎Maybe not.
‎But still,
‎I managed to distract you.
‎Right, Mole Rat?
‎Kim!
‎Oh, come on.
‎Did you just pull out a knife?
‎Can't handle me barehanded?
‎Bring it.
‎I can't be bothered.
‎Right.
‎The hero always shows up at the end.
‎You've got this, Taekwondo!
‎I guess you're not a total waste
‎of taxpayers' money.
‎Let's see how you fight on that leg.
‎Look, over there.
‎The director and Sung Han-soo
‎are facing off up ahead!
‎You brought guns, knives,
‎and‎ your friends, huh?
‎Shut up and bring it.
‎Have you ever gone bungee jumping?
‎Jeez, my back.
‎See you, Park Jin-cheol.
‎-Director!
‎-What should we do?
‎He can't swim, can he?
‎Is it my turn now?
‎Two, four,
‎six, eight, ten…
‎Fourteen total.
‎Let's do this.
‎I surrender.
‎Peace!
‎I want peace!
‎Min-ji.
‎Just be alive.
‎Please.
‎Hello?
‎I'm…
‎I'm in here!
‎Help! I'm in here!
‎JU GANG-CHAN'S LACKEY
‎You guys are in big trouble now.
‎Why the hell isn't Nam answering?
‎-Hey, Sang-man.
‎-Yes, boss?
‎Go to the warehouse and take a photo.
‎Not just of the body.
‎Take a selfie with it.
‎Hey.
‎You know what I mean, right?
‎Yes.
‎So you're saying
‎I should take a photo of the body first,
‎and then one of myself, right?
‎You idiot.
‎Take a selfie with the body like this.
‎Jeez.
‎You know what? Just forget it.
‎Get a haircut
‎so your brain can get some oxygen.
‎Or lose some weight.
‎Hey.
‎You're supposed to take a selfie
‎before you take a photo of the body.
‎Shut it.
‎I can't trust them to do anything.
‎Hey, Nam.
‎Why didn't you pick up?
‎Don't you miss me?
‎I was actually wondering
‎if I should send you a photo or not.
‎Just get to the point.
‎I called because I missed you, of course.
‎You still walking around
‎with that weasel-ass face?
‎Do you want to die?
‎Okay, okay. Jeez, you're scary.
‎I need to talk to Chairman Ju.
‎Put Chairman Ju… No, wait.
‎Put Gang-chan on the phone.
‎So you really do want to die.
‎Where are you?
‎That bastard's daughter
‎is the one who wants to die, not me.
‎She killed someone, you see.
‎If he doesn't want his precious daughter
‎to go to prison,
‎tell him to call me right now.
‎I'll take good care of the body
‎in the meantime.
‎What
‎WORTHLESS THUG
‎VOICE RECORDING
‎Are you saying you killed this student?
‎Tell me.
‎You can take care of the body, right?
‎You're scaring me.
‎Why are you asking me this?
‎Money isn't a problem.
‎I'll give you as much as you want.
‎No, forget it!
‎I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
‎Go away!
‎I was studying in the study room
‎and stepped out for a break
‎when she showed up
‎and started cursing me out.
‎So you killed her?
‎No, I didn't! She just…
‎All I did was nudge her out of the way,
‎but she just fell on her own.
‎I think she did it on purpose.
‎She was pulling an act
‎to scam me for medical bills.
‎Dad!
‎You know she's crazy.
‎She bullied me every day.
‎I didn't do anything wrong.
‎It wasn't my fault, Dad.
‎You have to be honest with me.
‎Be honest.
‎Did you…
‎kill her?
‎I think so.
‎If you wanted to kill her,
‎you should've asked me to do it.
‎I'd do anything for you.
‎I've always given you
‎whatever you asked for.
‎It really hurts
‎that you didn't come to me.
‎I'm sorry, Dad.
‎It's not a big deal.
‎It's okay.
‎Did you check if she was dead?
‎She was bleeding from her head,
‎but I'm not sure.
‎Golden Teeth has the body, right?
‎Yes.
‎Then make it so that ‎he‎ killed her.
‎Understood, sir.
‎Hello?
‎Please open the door!
‎Is anyone there?
‎Please open the door…
‎I'm cold…
‎Dad…
‎Who are you?
‎Jeez, you scared me.
‎Who are you, mister? Why are you here?
‎-Who the hell are you?
‎-I asked you a question!
‎NAME: KIM SANG-MAN
‎AGE: 41
‎Does this bastard
‎have wax in his ears or something?
‎I just asked who the hell you are!
‎What the hell's wrong with him?
‎You know whose phone this is, don't you?
‎Where is she?
‎You're putting me in a tough spot.
‎You asked for this, okay?
‎To the left.
‎Oh man.
‎Even a dead body
‎would freeze to death here.
‎Where did they put it?
‎JU GANG-CHAN
‎Goodness, Chairman.
‎How kind of you to call me.
‎I hope you're well.
‎Well, I suppose
‎you're in much better shape than me
‎since you only eat what's good for you.
‎Chief Nam filled me in.
‎I heard you did my daughter a favor.
‎Goodness, there are no favors between us.
‎How's your blonde-haired daughter doing?
‎They say early education
‎is important these days.
‎She takes after her father
‎and knows how to kill people
‎and get rid of bodies very well.
‎You raised a very smart daughter.
‎Let's talk in person.
‎Of course.
‎But…
‎stop talking down to me, asshole.
‎Don't you get it?
‎I'll send you an address.
‎Get your ass over here right now
‎with two billion won in cash.
‎And leave your lackeys behind.
‎Come alone.
‎Oh, and one more thing.
‎It's about Nam's teeth.
‎Pull them all out and bring them to me.
‎I'll need a photo as proof as well.
‎He won't be able to talk properly
‎without his teeth,
‎but tell him I'll give him
‎private lessons for that.
‎-Let's go.
‎-Yes, sir.
‎Let's go!
‎-Yes, sir!
‎SHARING LOCATION WITH KIM MIN-JI
‎23, Hangman 10-ro.
‎Damn, I really want to see that bastard
‎get his teeth yanked out.
‎Maybe I should've told him
‎to bring him here.
‎AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
‎I'm sorry.
‎I'll wait for you.
‎I don't have time for this. Bring it.
‎Don't you think we'll need weapons too?
‎So, his daughter is his weakness.
‎Spread out and search.
‎All we need is for Kim Min-ji
‎to disappear.
‎If you so much as lay a finger
‎on my daughter,
‎I'll kill you all.
‎I'm sorry, Dad.
‎Min-ji…
‎is alive.
‎Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim